Thank you for making time to visit, Sakuraba.
Of course.
As you can see,
my daughter has fully recovered now.
I'm sorry for the trouble we caused you.
Your photos turned out wonderful.
To think you would collapse at the ceremony.
And for an ulcer, no less.
Thank goodness we had a short guest list.
My, Kazuomi looks stunning in this shot.
Speaking of which, how are our guests faring?
Your friends must have been shocked.
I only hope no rumors have spread about this.
That won't be an issue, Mother.
My friends are trustworthy folks.
What a relief. If rumors were to spread,
I can only imagine how awkward
the office would get for you.
I want my daughter and son-in-law
to lead a life of happiness.
The venue was quite lovely as well.
It was.
You look beautiful here, Mom.
Do I?
Why did you tag along?
Because you mentioned Sayaka was discharged.
Did you already tell her?
About?
Are you kidding me?
About the poison,
and everything else we've found out.
Did you ask about the ConCafe?
What about those dating apps?
Of course not.
Sayaka would never. I won't believe it.
What are you two whispering about?
Sakuraba was expressing his relief
to see Sayaka well again.
Right.
Is that so?
You're welcome to stay for cake as well.
Thank you.
- Congrats!
- Congratulations!
I heard you took
their first-look photos as well?
That's right.
They're lucky to have found
a photographer like you.
He was a pro at work. It was amazing.
Yeah.
It's often a struggle
to capture natural expressions.
But watching them from my camera,
I could see they were in their own world.
Sayaka didn't seem too nervous, either.
Yeah.
I do enjoy taking first-look photos.
It lets me capture couples at their happiest.
All your shots turned out great.
I owe that all to my subjects.
Don't sell yourself short.
How else could you capture two strangers
having such a natural moment together?
Cameras help me see the truth in people,
that's all.
What, is that a superpower of yours?
No, no.
It's just a side effect
that comes with the profession.
You're an amazing guy.
Sayaka?
Sayaka? Are you feeling ill?
Sorry, it's just another dizzy spell.
It's nothing serious.
You should lie down for a bit.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
I apologize for the scene, Sakuraba.
You're free to stay and finish that slice.
Right, thank you.
The poisoned bride is now in the company
of two prime suspects.
I can't believe this ceremony's on a weekday.
Yeah, seriously.
Let's go for a smoke.
They'll get divorced anyway.
No human being is without ill will.
And that includes the suspect-hunting groom.
Great work out there.
Likewise, Ueno.
Though I know you already have our old one,
here's our new business card, for posterity.
- Thanks, I appreciate it.
- Anytime.
[Bridging true love and virtue]
[Honoka Ueno]
"Virtue", huh?
That reminds me.
The Hayashida couple visited again.
The wife seemed to be doing better.
Is that so.
That's wonderful to hear.
I suppose the violin performance
really stressed her out.
What?
Mrs. Sayaka didn't seem eager to perform.
But she said her mother insisted.
It seems now the couple
wish to redo their ceremony.
Really? Redo it, you say.
Sayaka has always been timid.
It made her a magnet for trouble.
She brought chaos
into my otherwise stable life.
It feels so nice out.
But I have no regrets marrying her.
Pretty, aren't they?
However...
I'm sorry.
I...
I ruined our wedding.
No one blames you, Sayaka.
I'll be at your side, to protect you.
I keep adding to your troubles.
It's all my fault.
I made you handle the house by yourself.
And you still visited me every day.
Jeez. Don't worry about me, alright?
Say, Kazu.
What did you do while I was in the hospital?
What?
I was... well...
I was missing every moment without you.
I'm so grateful you're better now.
Shall we?
Aw, really?
[Meet me downstairs]
Looks like you could use some fresh air.
I'll protect you.
No matter who you are.
Sorry, did I wake you up?
No.
Can't sleep?
Nah.
Here, lie down.
Good night.
No matter who she is...
Right.
[Chie: How are you? Let's meet up again.]
The first wedding that resulted in poison.
Unraveling the bride's past.
Especially with her job at the ConCafe.
She had relationships
with several of her customers.
She sought out solace in dating apps as well.
And now...
A second wedding.
He now knows of his wife's "impurities",
yet pushes for a do-over. Why?
It's all the more perplexing,
given what I know of him.
ConCafe?
That's practically like working the nightlife.
Don't act like you have good intentions.
Did he know of his wife's past already?
Of course not.
Really?
What do you think he's really like?
His anger was intense.
This all happened
before he even met the woman.
Why do you think he's so volatile,
Sachiko?
Guess we won't know unless we ask.
Seriously?
- Morning.
- Good morning.
Sorry I took such a long break.
It's no worries at all.
So, how was your time off?
What do you mean?
You spent time with your wife, right?
Of course I did.
What?
Just wondering if you two
did anything special.
Not really.
Is that so?
Good to know.
Come here.
Quick.
Something definitely happened.
Hey, what's the occasion?
I think rumors are spreading.
What?
About the wedding.
You knew about this?
I mean...
Well, did you?
Word about it spread to my department.
Seriously?
Some of my juniors even asked about it.
What did they want to know?
They just asked if I attended your wedding.
And if Sayaka truly "collapsed at the altar".
You've got to be kidding me.
I still don't know who started the rumor.
But hey, don't let it get to you.
Easy for you to say.
I worry about people being judgemental.
The rumor will die out in due time.
How can you be so sure?
"Yes, I attended the ceremony.
But no one collapsed."
"I think there's been a misunderstanding."
That's what I've been telling everyone.
People will forget about this soon enough.
Naoto...
You're such a great guy. Seriously, thanks.
Who the hell even started this rumor?
I'm blessed to have a friend like you.
I am Sayaka's best friend.
Everything I've done, is for Sayaka's sake.
You owe me a meal, alright?
Your best friend just saved your skin.
Naoto.
Just to get this out there,
you didn't start the rumor, right?
Kazuomi.
That's not funny, man.
I wanted to be sure.
You've always been like this.
Learn some tact already.
- I just...
- Sure, you're frustrated with what happened.
But that's no reason to take it out on me.
I never meant to...
It's even worse if you didn't mean it.
That's the sort of thing
that eventually escalates to harassment.
What?
You better not be making Sayaka cry
with that sort of attitude, too.
No, I would never.
Harassment is despicable.
A girl like her chose to marry you.
Quit acting so self-centered,
and learn to prioritize Sayaka already.
I do prioritize Sayaka.
I know she relies on you.
But don't think you're so above it all,
just because you're the husband.
Sayaka's a nice girl.
Don't take advantage of her.
I won't.
And I know I've mentioned this before,
but inviting them to the wedding was just...
I get it already.
Before you doubt me,
watch yourself, alright?
Just drop it.
I'm not talking about your attitude.
Someone's looking into you, Kazuomi.
What? Who?
That guy who was at the wedding.
The photographer you hired.
What?
Might just be me overthinking it though.
It's him. He spread the rumors.
He betrayed me.
Why are you snooping around?
What are you referring to?
You were at my office. Why?
Did you tell my coworkers about the wedding?
Huh?
You told them about Sayaka collapsing,
didn't you?
What would I gain by doing that?
Remember, we're searching for the culprit.
I was looking into one of our suspects.
You, as a matter of fact.
What?
I was asking around about the suspect,
Kazuomi Hayashida.
You're the one who poisoned the bride,
are you not?
You think I did it?
Why?
Your beloved wife has a history.
She's seen other men in her life.
Perhaps you felt particularly vengeful.
Oh, yes. I heard the good news.
A second wedding, was it?
What's your next plot?
Will you test your luck again?
Shut your damn mouth.